Thomas Rasor

Contact

thomas.ir.rasor@gmail.com (254) 291 2646 Austin, TX – 78729

Skills

Programming

- C#, .NET
- GLSL / HLSL
- VB, SQL
- Python
- GDScript

UI / UX Design

Database Management & Interaction Office 365

- SharePoint
- PowerApps
- Power Automate Flows
- · Microsoft Office Suite

Photoshop

Video Editing & VFX Music & Sound Design Game Development

- Unity
- Unreal
- Godot

Education

Austin Community College

1 yr. - Game Design

4 yr. - Computer Science

Overview

As a self-taught programmer since my early teens, I've spent a decade honing my skills in game and software development. I've worked with various game engines, including Unreal Engine and Godot, but my true passion lies in pushing the Unity engine to its limits. My expertise centers on graphics programming and user interface design. I've enhanced my UI/UX skills in a professional setting at Accenture since 2018.

Experience

Technical Artist - 2014-2017

Tanzle Inc

Remote at Tanzle Inc, I helped pioneer early VR, AR, and other stereoscopic viewing focused projects, collaborating with technology leaders in the field. From crafting museum installations to developing hospital visualization software, I swiftly transitioned from experimentation to deployment, exercising a high level of autonomy.

Ads Content Reviewer - 2018-2020

Accenture

As an Advertising Content Reviewer for Accenture, I worked with a team to implement, refine, and ensure the proficiency of numerous policies aimed at improving end user advertising experiences as well as meeting advertiser satisfaction across our client's advertising network.

Reporting Analyst / WFM Lead – 2020-Current

Accenture

After working as a Content Reviewer for 2 years, I moved up to manage the roster for the entire project of around 400 resources. I have had a myriad of responsibilities under this role, including generating analytical reports but also handling the virtual paperwork for new hires, attrition, and more. I was also able to design and implement numerous small applications to help our team do their work more efficiently and intelligently by using Microsoft's PowerApps and SharePoint integrations.